businessandlifetips.com 2019-03-31

# PRIVACY POLICY - Business and Life Tips

Business and Life Tips ( We, Us, Our) is committed to protecting our user’s information and to making our users aware of our online practices regarding the privacy of their information. By visiting this website (blog), you expressly consent and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

This blog does not share personal information with third parties nor do we store any information about your visit to this blog other than to analyse and optimize your content and reading experience through the use of cookies. You can turn off the use of cookies at anytime by changing your specific browser settings.

We are not responsible for republished content from this blog on other blogs or websites without our permission.

We may collect personal information when you provide it to us by submitting to the site content on the blog requesting email updates and newsletters. Business and life may collect personal information in connection therewith such as your name, email address or even phone number.

We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information online from minors, if we learn that a minor has submitted personal identifiable information online in contravention of these measures we will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from the databases and not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the minor or others as required by the Law).

This site/blog may provide links to other websites that we may think are useful. Business and Life Tips is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites.

We may use outside companies to display ads on this blog. These ads and notices may contain cookies. Third parties also may post content to our site. These postings may also contain cookies.  
More details on our privacy policy can be found  [here. ](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/businessandlifetips.com)  
This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and was last updated on 3rd January, 2017. If you have any questions feel free to contact us directly here: john@businessandlifetips.com
